blackboardeats.com 2015-03-18

# Privacy Policy

BlackboardEats.com (the "Site" or "we") has adopted this Privacy Policy because we are committed to protecting your privacy. By using the Site you agree to this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy is effective as of November 21, 2013.

If you choose to visit the Site, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and the Site's Terms and Conditions, including limitations on damages, jurisdiction of disputes and application of the law of the State of California.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at privacy@blackboardeats.com or write to us at: 

BlackboardEats, LLC  
2554 Lincoln Blvd., #352  
Venice, CA 90291 

The Information You Provide To Us. In order for you to access certain services that we offer via the Site, such as restaurant reviews, access to Specials and our Guide, we may require you to provide us with certain information that personally identifies you, such as your name, e-mail address and zip code. We will use this information to verify your identity or provide you with e-mail notice of exciting offers. To enable payment for and delivery of goods or services that we provide, we may request billing, credit card and mailing information. In connection with contests, sweepstakes and other activities that we make available, we may collect other information, including your contact data. From time to time, we may also request that you voluntarily complete questionnaires relevant to our business and ask you for demographic information. WE WILL PROTECT THIS AND ANY OTHER PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION THAT YOU PROVIDE TO US IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS POLICY.

Accessing the Site. When you request a page within the Site, our web servers automatically recognize your domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed the Site. We may provide this information to other companies and individuals to perform functions on behalf the Site. This information may be used to examine our traffic in aggregate and to investigate misuse of the Site or to cooperate with law enforcement.

Cookies. From time to time, the Site or its advertisers may send a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other Web sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to identify which areas of the Site you have visited or customized, so the next time you visit those pages they may be readily accessible. Along with our advertisers, we may also use cookies to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement and to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you see on our site. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. You can reset your browser to provide a Do Not Track signal and to refuse all cookies, or you can allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our Site and other websites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended. 

You can unsubscribe from receiving our e-mails at any time. You can unsubscribe by clicking on the "Unsubscribe" link in the footer of any e-mail and following the instructions. You can also unsubscribe by clicking on the "Unsubscribe" link on the bottom of the Site and following the instructions. 

We will disclose Your Personally Identifiable Information and/or an IP address, when required by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * 1\. Conform to the law or comply with legal process served on us, 

  * 2\. Protect and defend the rights or property of the Site, or visitors to the Site and related properties, 

  * 3\. Identify persons who may be violating the law, the Site's Terms and Conditions, the rights of third parties, or otherwise misusing the Site or its related properties, 

  * 4\. Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities.

In addition, BBE may provide such information to third parties if it is necessary to fulfill requests of BBE Subscribers to purchase goods or services on or through the site; for purposes of servicing BBE business lines or facilities; or in connection with the sale of all or part of BBE’s ownership interests, businesses or assets, or the sale, license or other transfer of all or part of any products or services that BBE provides or develops, and any rights thereto. In all such events, BBE will require that any transferee of such information protect it in accordance with this privacy policy.

We may allow third parties to advertise on the Site. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the business and privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage you to be aware of this when you leave the Site and to read the legal notices and privacy policies of each and every website you visit.

We have reasonable security measures in place and technologies to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of your information under our control but we cannot assure that Your Personally Identifiable Information or non-personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. Furthermore, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive the information. 

The Site serves general users of the World Wide Web. We support and comply with the Children's Online Protection Act (COPPA) and we do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13, nor do we share such information with third parties. Children under the age of 18 may use the Site only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

We make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We will ask that you identify yourself and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. To access, correct or delete your personal information, contact: [privacy@blackboardeats.com](mailto:privacy@blackboardeats.com). 

We may amend and revise this Privacy Policy from time to time, and in the event of material changes, we will post notice on our Homepage so that you may read our revised Privacy Policy. Subscribers continued use of the Site constitutes acceptance of our revised Privacy Policy. If you would like to be notified by e-mail if and when material changes are made to this Privacy Policy, please opt in to receiving such e-mail notifications by contacting us at [privacy@blackboardeats.com](mailto:privacy@blackboardeats.com).
